Guide to the Polly Shackleton papers, 1894-1997 MS2031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1900-1995; MS2031 Series 6; 15 Linear feet
  - Plaque, "2nd Annual D.C.P.A. Award for Public Service presented to Council member Polly Shackleton and Staff, for courageous and effective leadership in benefit of the public which resulted in the enactment of the 'Health-Care and Community Residence Facility Hospice and Home Care Licensure Act of 1983' District of Columbia Psychological Association, 1984 January 15 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid:] Note: rusty Swiss-army pocket knife at top of plaque
  - Trophy, Elizabeth and David Scull Metropolitan Service Award to Polly Shackleton, 1985 December 11 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Passport, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1927 May 27 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Special Passport, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1955 April 29 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Passport, Issued to Polly Shackleton, 1955 May 02 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Passport, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1957 August 05 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - International Driving Permit, Issued to Polly Shackleton, 1957 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - International Driving Permit, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1957 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Passport, Issued to Polly Shackleton, 1961 August 04 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Passport, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1961 August 04 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Passport, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1966 June 22 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Passport, Issued to Polly Shackleton, 1971 November 26 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Passport, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1971 November 26 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Passport, Issued to Robert Shackleton, 1977 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Passport, Issued to Polly Shackleton, 1977 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Passport, Issued to Polly Shackleton, 1983 June 23 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Passport, Issued to Polly Shackleton, 1993 May 03 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan police issued identification card, 1982 March 04 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    "Poly Shackleton D.C. Council Member Ward 3 by virtue of his office he shall be permitted to pass through police lines..."
  - 1959 Miniature day planner, initials P. E. S. on front cover (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 1963 Miniature day planner (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1964 Miniature day planner (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 1965 Miniature day planner (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 1966 Miniature day planner (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1967 Miniature day planner (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Large plaque, "To the Honorable Polly Shackleton for your many years of exceptional leadership in government, politics and our community ... presented ... from the District of Columbia Democratic State Committee...", 1986 May 01 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Large plaque, "Metropolitan Washington Public Health Association presents the 1980 Annual Award to Polly Shackleton...", undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Large plaque, "To Polly Shackleton ... [from] International Church Ushers Association of D.C., Inc. ...", 1970 February (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Large plaque, "Honorable Polly Shackleton for her support and assistance with the lead elimination activities in the District of Columbia, Committee for L.E.A.D.", 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Large plaque, "Award of Recognition presented to Polly Shackleton Council Member ... at the 43rd Annual Convention of the National Bar Association...", 1968 July 31 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Large plaque, "Certificate of Appreciation, Senior Citizens Counseling and Delivery Services Sincerely Appreciates Honorable Polly Shackleton...", 1980 December 09 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Campaign poster, "United Democrats for Johnson.. .Polly Shackleton.", undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Campaign poster, "Re-Elect Polly Shackleton City Council Ward 3.. .", undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Enlarged newspaper article- "District's First Office Opened in SE", undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Enlarged newspaper article photograph- "Councilwoman Polly Shackleton at meeting with Senior Citizens on May 22, 1968.", 1968 May 22 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Enlarged photograph with inscription, "To Polly, with deep appreciation for your participation in our 25th anniversary, Capt. J.J. Crawder, U.S. Navy Commanding Officer.", undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Poster with caricature of Polly Shackleton; "Rare Greek Fragment Found", undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Framed certificate, "Lyndon B. Johnson to Polly Shackleton,... membership of the District of Columbia Council", 1967 November 01 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Framed certificate, "Government of the District of Columbia.. .Polly Shackleton was duly elected Ward 3 Member", 1975 January 02 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Framed certificate, "Government of the District of Columbia... Polly Shackleton was duly elected Ward 3 Member", 1979 January 02 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - "Time Magazine - Man of the Year", undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    glass cover broken
  - Framed certificate, "For the Love of Children presents this Certificate of Appreciation to the Honorable Polly Shackleton...", 1985 June 15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Framed award, "1967, The Holiday Award for a Beautiful America, Honorable Mention, Project Pride of Washington, D.C. for Commendable Efforts to Conserve and Improve Our Environment, Caskie Stinnett, editor." (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - four photographs of Polly at a typewriter, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    corresponding photographs unframed located in photograph series of the collection
  - "Polly Shackleton, Changing Times Gallery, 03/1993", 1993 March (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Polly in background, center-right
  - Framed photo, Polly Shackleton and Hubert Humphrey, autographed, "To Polly Shackleton- with my warm regards and appreciation, Hubert Humphrey.", undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Framed photo, man in plaid jacket (Robert Shackleton?), undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Guest book, "The Citizens Advisory Council of IONA House Senior Services Celebrates Polly Shackleton's Contribution to the Quality of Life for Older Citizens in the District of Columbia", 1986 December 10 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - "Washington Is A Capital City.": button, undated; Item 1
    - "Washington Is A Capital City.": button, undated; Item 2
    - "We're Not Getting Older", "We're Getting Better", Senior Fellowship: button, undated; Item 3
    - 1929-1968, 1968 Poor Peoples Campaign, Washington, D.C., NPCA-SCLC, Item 4
    - Peace, Equality, Justice: button, 1986; Item 5
    - Peace, Equality, Justice: button, 1986; Item 6
    - 4-H Booster: button, undated; Item 7
    - 4-H Member: button, undated; Item 8
    - A Winner for All Washington, Jerry Moore: button, undated; Item 9
    - A Winner for All Washington, Jerry Moore: button, undated; Item 10
    - Adlai: button, undated; Item 11
    - Adlai and Estes; Adlai, Estes, and Joe Smith: button, undated; Item 12
    - Advisory Councils Yes!: button, undated; Item 13
    - Advisory Councils Yes!: button, undated; Item 14
    - AFGE For Mondale: button, undated; Item 15
  - Buttons, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - AIDS is a Social Work issue: button, undated; Item 1
    - All The Way With LBJ: button, undated; Item 2
    - American flag border, Franklin Delano Roosevelt: button, undated; Item 3
    - American flag pin: button, undated; Item 4
    - April 22, environment: button, undated; Item 5
    - April 22, environment: button, undated; Item 6
    - Arrington Dixon, Chairman: button, undated; Item 7
    - Association for Retarded Citizens, District of Columbia, Full Citizenship: button, undated; Item 8
    - B'Nai B'Rith, Join-In, A Membership Happening: button, undated; Item 9
    - Bentsen in 76: button, undated; Item 10
    - Bike for a Better City (blue): button, undated; Item 11
    - Bike for a Better City (yellow): button, undated; Item 12
    - Black background, man and woman with white and green masks: button, undated; Item 13
    - Black background, white circle with bar through it: button, undated; Item 14
    - Black border, red center with gold image of Capitol building: button, undated; Item 15
    - Bronze pin with blue and red beads and Buddha figure: button, undated; Item 16
    - Campaign '72 McGovern Staff Headquarters: button, 1972; Item 17
  - Buttons, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Carter, Mondale: button, undated; Item 1
    - CCCP, 2 - I - 1959: button, undated; Item 2
    - Celebrate the City, Beyond the Monuments, 200 Years, Washington, D.C.: button, undated; Item 3
    - Children's Survival, March 25, Washington, D.C.: button, undated; Item 4
    - Clinton, Gore, Rapid Response Team: button, undated; Item 5
    - Common Cause: button, undated; Item 6
    - D.C. Federation, Scholarship Fund Booster, Civic Associations: button, undated; Item 7
    - D.C. Honors, Astronaut, Frederick Drew Gregory: button, undated; Item 8
    - D.C. Youth Symphony Orchestra, International Festival, St. Moritz, Switzerland: button, 1970 August; Item 9
    - DC Campaign For A Nuclear Weapons Freeze, Initiative 10, Vote YES Nov. 2: button, undated; Item 10
    - DCGH, I Care About Health Care: button, undated; Item 11
    - Deal With The Problems, Build the Model City With Soul: button, undated; Item 12
    - Democratic National Convention, San Francisco: button, 1984 July 16-19; Item 13
  - Buttons, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Democrats Care: button, undated; Item 1
    - District of Columbia City Council: button, undated; Item 2
    - Don't Discriminate, Educate! OHR: button, undated; Item 3
    - Don't tear it down: button, undated; Item 4
    - Don't Tear It Down: button, undated; Item 5
    - Don't Tear It Down: button, undated; Item 6
    - Drug Free D.C.: button, undated; Item 7
    - Dukakis, Bentsen: button, undated; Item 8
    - Eaton School, 34 St. Art Fair: button, undated; Item 9
    - Ed Muskie: button, undated; Item 10
    - Eleanor Holmes Norton for Congress: button, undated; Item 11
    - Eleanor Holmes Norton for Congress: button, undated; Item 12
    - Elect John Ray, D.C. Council-At-Large: button, undated; Item 13
    - Elect John Ray, D.C. Council-At-Large: button, undated; Item 14
    - Election '84 Women Hold the Key: button, 1984; Item 15
    - Environment!: button, undated; Item 16
  - Buttons, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fauntroy: button, undated; Item 1
    - Fauntroy: button, undated; Item 2
    - Fauntroy '76: button, 1976; Item 3
    - Fauntroy for Congress: button, undated; Item 4
    - Fauntroy, Congress: button, undated; Item 5
    - Fauntroy, Congress: button, undated; Item 6
    - Firebird, Fever!: button, undated; Item 7
    - Floc: button, undated; Item 8
    - Food for Christmas Drive: button, 1984; Item 9
    - Free Angela: button, undated; Item 10
    - Friend of Ruth (202) 347-9689: button, undated; Item 11
    - GASP for Clean Air: button, undated; Item 12
    - Gemini: button, undated; Item 13
    - Get With It, Washington Urban League: button, undated; Item 14
    - Get With It, Washington Urban League: button, undated; Item 15
    - Gold colored button with letter 'A': button, undated; Item 16
    - Gold medallion, red Chinese lettering, blue, green, and gold image of the Great Wall of China: button, undated; Item 17
    - Green background, white castle image in center: button, undated; Item 18
    - Have You Thanked A Green Tree Today?: button, undated; Item 19
  - Buttons, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Helping you put knowledge to work, Cooperative Extension: button, undated; Item 1
    - HHH: button, undated; Item 2
    - HHH: button, undated; Item 3
    - HHH Humphrey: button, undated; Item 4
    - Hogs Are Beautiful: button, undated; Item 5
    - Home Rule Now, undated; Item 6
    - I Am A Consumer, 727-1158 Treat Me Right 727-1158: button, undated; Item 7
    - I Am An Anacostian: button, undated; Item 8
    - I Am An Anacostian: button, undated; Item 9
    - I Gave to Project Harvest: button, undated; Item 10
    - I Gave to the IRS: button, undated; Item 11
    - I Have A Dream, Let Freedom Ring, A Great American, Rev. Martin Luther King, Jan. 15, 1929 - April 4, 1968: button, undated; Item 12
    - I have an idea!: button, undated; Item 13
    - I Have True Grit: button, undated; Item 14
    - I Love 4-H: button, undated; Item 15
    - I love the 1962 Buick Skylark, Happy 25th: button, 1987; Item 16
    - I Ride Metro: button, 1976; Item 17
    - I Ride Metro: button, 1976; Item 18
  - Buttons, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - I stand with Marion Barry: button, undated; Item 1
    - I Vote, Shouldn't You?: button, undated; Item 2
    - I Voted: button, undated; Item 3
    - I Voted: button, undated; Item 4
    - I Voted: button, undated; Item 5
    - I'm A Believer: button, undated; Item 6
    - I'm Energetic: button, undated; Item 7
    - I'm for No-Fault: button, undated; Item 8
    - I'm for No-Fault: button, undated; Item 9
    - I'm for No-Fault: button, undated; Item 10
    - I'm for No-Fault: button, undated; Item 11
    - I'm For the Bottle Bill: button, undated; Item 12
    - I'm Helping Smokey! Prevent Forest Fires: button, undated; Item 13
    - Inaugural Committee, Mrs. Polly Shackleton, Co-Chairman - Housing: button, undated; Item 14
    - Interspace works: button, undated; Item 15
    - IONA House Volunteer, Senior Services: button, undated; Item 16
  - Buttons, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - IOWNA Future!: button, undated; Item 1
    - It Takes A Woman... A Democrat: button, 1974; Item 2
    - Jim Nathanson, Effective Leadership, D.C. Council/Ward 3: button, undated; Item 3
    - Jim Nathanson, Effective Leadership, D.C. Council/Ward 3: button, undated; Item 4
    - Jim Symington, Democrat: button, undated; Item 5
    - Jimmy Carter: button, undated; Item 6
    - Jimmy Carter, Walter Mondale, Leaders, for a change, Vote Democrat: button, undated; Item 7
    - Johnson - Humphrey, Vote Democrat: button, undated; Item 8
    - Join the Underground: button, undated; Item 9
    - June 19, Solidarity Day: button, undated; Item 10
    - Juror, Superior Court, District of Columbia: button, 1972; Item 11
    - Kane... of course!: button, undated; Item 12
    - Keep the Lid on Lead: button, undated; Item 13
    - Ken: button, undated; Item 14
    - Kennedy for President (hologram image): button, undated; Item 15
    - LBJ for the USA (hologram image pin), undated; Item 16
  - Buttons, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Leaders, for a change, Carter, Mondale: button, undated; Item 1
    - Leaders, for a change, Carter, Mondale: button, undated; Item 2
    - Leaving A World Where Butterflies Can Fly Free: button, undated; Item 3
    - Liberal and Proud of it!: button, undated; Item 4
    - Lowenstein Won: button, undated; Item 5
    - Lynn Yeakel, U.S. Senate: button, undated; Item 6
    - Maintain 18 D.C. Drinking Age: button, undated; Item 7
    - make a date for '88: button, undated; Item 8
    - make a date for '88: button, undated; Item 9
    - March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom: button, 1963 August 28; Item 10
    - Marion Barry Council At Large: button, undated; Item 11
    - Mayor Barry for ONE Washington: button, 1986 May 17; Item 12
    - Mayor Barry, Making a great city even greater: button, undated; Item 13
    - McGovern: button, undated; Item 14
  - Buttons, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - McGovern: button, undated; Item 1
    - McGovern: button, undated; Item 2
    - McGovern: button, undated; Item 3
    - McGovern '72: button, undated; Item 4
    - McGovern on red, white, and blue background: button, undated; Item 5
    - McGovern on red, white, and blue background: button, undated; Item 6
    - McGovern, Green background, white circle with bar through it: button, undated; Item 7
    - Melina Mercouri is a Greek: button, undated; Item 8
    - MICCO, Micco Citizen Planner: button, undated; Item 9
    - Mikva!: button, undated; Item 10
    - Missing in Asia, Who Cares? We Care!: button, undated; Item 11
    - Mondale: button, undated; Item 12
    - Mondale: button, undated; Item 13
    - Muskie!: button, undated; Item 14
    - My Heart Belongs To Jarvis, Leading The City Home: button, undated; Item 15
    - National Tenants Organization: button, undated; Item 16
    - National Town Meeting, Mobil: button, undated; Item 17
    - No. 1 Sugar Ray: button, undated; Item 18
    - Nurses are good for your Political Health: button, undated; Item 19
    - Orange background, three children dancing on pink map of United States: button, undated; Item 20
    - Oregon needs MORSE, undated; Item 21
  - Buttons, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Partnership for Change, Re-elect Fauntroy, Let's Do It Here First: button, undated; Item 1
    - PAT for First Lady: button, undated; Item 2
    - Peabody for Vice President: button, undated; Item 3
    - Peabody for Vice President: button, undated; Item 4
    - Polly Shackleton for D.C. Council: button, undated; Item 5
    - Polly Shackleton for D.C. Council: button, undated; Item 6
    - Polly Shackleton, Councilwoman: button, undated; Item 7
    - Polly Shackleton, Hostess ribbon: button, undated; Item 8
    - Poor People's Campaign, 1968; Item 9
    - Prevent Homelessness, Strengthen Rent Control, Coalition for the Homeless: button, undated; Item 10
    - Project Pride: button, undated; Item 11
    - Project Pride: button, undated; Item 12
    - Read the Daily Gazette, Vote: button, undated; Item 13
    - Red background in the shape of a bow, gold colored center with raised relief of Lenin's profile: button, undated; Item 14
    - Re-elect Arrington Dixon 4 Councilman: button, undated; Item 15
    - Re-elect Arrington Dixon 4 Councilman: button, undated; Item 16
    - Re-Elect Charlene Drew Jarvis, Ward 4: button, undated; Item 17
    - Re-elect Congresswoman Eleanor Holmes Norton, undated; Item 18
  - Buttons, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Re-elect Councilman Wilson, Ward 2, He Gets Things Done: button, undated; Item 1
    - Re-elect Councilman Wilson, Ward 2, He Gets Things Done: button, undated; Item 2
    - Re-elect Councilmember H.R. Crawford, Ward 7 D.C. Council: button, undated; Item 3
    - Re-elect Douglas, The People's Senator: button, undated; Item 4
    - Re-elect Jack Evans, Ward 2 City Council: button, undated; Item 5
    - Re-elect John Ray: button, undated; Item 6
    - Re-elect Marion Barry, City Council '76, 1976; Item 7
    - Re-elect Marion Barry, City Council '76, 1976; Item 8
    - Re-elect R. David Hall, D.C. School Board, Ward 2: button, undated; Item 9
    - Re-elect Wanda Washburn, D.C. School Board, Ward 3: button, undated; Item 10
    - Re-elect Wilhelmina Rolark, D.C. Council Ward 8: button, undated; Item 11
    - Re-elect Wilson, Ward 2: button, undated; Item 12
    - Re-elect Wilson, Ward 2: button, undated; Item 13
    - Route to Victory, Route to Greatness, Vote Democratic '66: button, undated; Item 14
    - Save A Life, Sign A Card: button, undated; Item 15
    - Save our coast: button, undated; Item 16
    - Save our coast, undated; Item 17
  - Buttons, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Save our Kids, Save the Hurt Home: button, undated; Item 1
    - Shanghi: button, undated; Item 2
    - Ship the GIs home now!: button, undated; Item 3
    - Sickles: button, undated; Item 4
    - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, Commission on Mental Health Services, 1987 October 01; Item 5
    - Stevenson: button, undated; Item 6
    - Stevenson: button, undated; Item 7
    - Support Bill 2-108, Rights For Mentally Retarded Citizens: button, undated; Item 8
    - Support Friendship Terrace: button, undated; Item 9
    - Take back the Senate with Independent Action.: button, undated; Item 10
    - The Death Penalty Is Dead Wrong: button, undated; Item 11
    - Think Soup, La Potagerie: button, undated; Item 12
    - Three beaded rings: 1) green and orange; 2) green and red; 3) green and red: button, undated; Item 13
    - Two beaded rings: 1) green and black; 2) blue, green, and yellow: button, undated; Item 14
    - Two beaded rings: 1) orange and blue; 2) yellow, black, blue, and red: button, undated; Item 15
    - Tilia Cordata: button, undated; Item 16
    - Tucker. Mayor. Now: button, undated; Item 17
    - Tuition Tax Credits: button, undated; Item 18
  - Buttons, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Department of the Interior, FWPCA, Clean Water: button, undated; Item 1
    - United Nations' Decade for women, 1978-1986; Item 2
    - Unity 76: button, undated; Item 3
    - USSR Photo 76: button, undated; Item 4
    - Vote "for" Referendum 001, For Rent Control: button, undated; Item 5
    - Vote in 1994 Sharon Pratt Kelly, Mayor, Washington, D.C., Item 6
    - Vote July 19th Hilda Mason Councilwoman At-Large: button, undated; Item 7
    - Vote July 19th Hilda Mason Councilwoman At-Large: button, undated; Item 8
    - Vote Mayor Barry, September 14th: button, undated; Item 9
    - Vote Mayor Barry, September 14th: button, undated; Item 10
    - Vote to End the War: button, undated; Item 11
    - Vote to End the War: button, undated; Item 12
    - Vozy Voto: button, undated; Item 13
    - W76, Win With Women, 1976; Item 14
    - Wait in the Weeds Gang: button, undated; Item 15
    - War on Rats, I Cooperate: button, undated; Item 16
    - War on Rats, I Cooperate: button, undated; Item 17
    - Washington '84, it's logica., undated; Item 18
  - Buttons, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Washington Dulles International Airport, 1962-1992, Item 1
    - Washington for Washington: button, undated; Item 2
    - We Care for Children: button, undated; Item 3
    - We Care for Children: button, undated; Item 4
    - We Still Have A Dream, Jobs, Peace, Freedom, March on Washington, 1983 August 27; Item 5
    - We Try Harder: button, undated; Item 6
    - We Try Harder: button, undated; Item 7
    - We're Putting Our Stamp On Washington: button, undated; Item 8
    - We're the People for Mondale, Ferraro, 800-258-6700: button, undated; Item 9
    - WEF, Fauntroy: button, undated; Item 10
    - WEF, Fauntroy: button, undated; Item 11
    - Welfare Rights NOW, NWRO: button, undated; Item 12
    - White background, gold colored horse in center: button, undated; Item 13
    - White background, gold outline of hands holding a castle: button, undated; Item 14
    - White background, pink and green pinwheel, undated; Item 15
  - Buttons, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - White background, red Arabic lettering: button, undated; Item 1
    - White background, red female symbol with equal sign inside: button, undated; Item 2
    - White background, red flame on top of blue logs, 1969; Item 3
    - Wilson, Council Chairman: button, undated; Item 4
    - Women to Reelect Marion Barry: button, undated; Item 5
    - Women to Reelect Marion Barry: button, undated; Item 6
    - Y.O.U. for HOME RULE in D.C., Youth Organizations United: button, undated; Item 7
    - Yeldell: button, undated; Item 8
    - Yellow background, five figures with fists raised in the air: button, undated; Item 9
    - Yes!: button, undated; Item 10
    - You Can Depend on Jerry Moore: button, undated; Item 11
    - You Can Depend on Jerry Moore: button, undated; Item 12
    - Young for Congress: button, undated; Item 13
    - ZAIS, Ward 2: button, undated; Item 14
    - Unknown woman, undated; Item 15
  - Blue cardboard, "Mrs. Polly Shackleton", undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Blue circle, "Walking with Stevenson", undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Cardboard circle, "Bound for the Democratic Convention in Greater Chicago", undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Cardboard circle, "Stevenson for President", undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Cassette tape, "In Memory, Polly Shackleton, 1910-1997", Circa 1997 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Cloth, "Gladly for Adlai", undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Voter's Registration Stub, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia Armory Board Courtesy Card, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 8)